appsfuel.com 2013-06-01

# AppsFuel End User License Agreement

* * *

These are the privacy principles that Appsfuel adheres to.

1\. You can control your data. If you don't have an AppsFuel user account, we do not store your personal data like text logs, buddies, passwords, etc. If you opt to sign up for an AppsFuel account, we store your usernames and passwords to automatically log you into your stored services. Future AppsFuel features may require us to store additional data, but we will only do so to enable the features you choose. 

2\. AppsFuel respects the privacy of its users. We will not share, sell, or give away your data. We hate spam and don't want you to get any because of AppsFuel. This document explains how AppsFuel will use the information that you provide to us via the Websites and the web app. 

3\. Information collected

3.1 You are not required to provide personally identifiable information to visit the Websites and the web app; however, in order to access third-party Apps, you may be required to enter your applicable user name(s) and password(s) but in such a case the owner of these Apps will be the processor and the process of your persona data will be done according to the third party App privacy policy.

In order to use the basic services of the third-party Apps, AppsFuel does not automatically store your user name(s) or password(s) on our server. If you wish to utilize advanced features of the marketplace Appsfuel , the , storage by us of your name(s), password(s) cell phone or other mobile device whether provided by your other service providers or yourself, etc may be necessary. AppsFuel may inform you by a screen message and ask you to confirm your election to have your information stored on our servers before doing so. In addition, to further enhance your user experience AppsFuel may collect usage data and other information on all users , but it is for service optimization purposes only, except as described below under the IP Addresses section (and specifically not for resale purposes). It may also include information supplied by your browser when accessing our Apps, such as IP address, type of browser, date and time of access, location when accessing the Website, our web app and/or the services etc. 

4\. Editing Registration Data

4.1 You may review and edit the information input by you when registering with the Appsfuel marketplace by using your e-mail address or User ID and Password. If you cancel your account, you may also have such registration data deleted from AppsFuel's database by sending your request to help(at)Appsfuel.com. You should also be aware that even if you delete your registration data, there may remain residual information that will remain within AppsFuel's databases, access logs and/or other records, which may or may not contain personal information and which can be used only for limited purposes listed in the point 8 below.

5.Cookies and Web Beacons

5.1 AppsFuel may use Cookies and Web Beacons on the Websites and the web app.

5.2 Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer's hard drive by our servers to identify your computer to our servers., No personally identifiable information stored in the AppsFuel cookies will be shared with outside companies for any purpose without your permission. You can also disable cookies or otherwise manage them through tools provided with your browser software and with third-party software packages, or simply not use the features that require Cookies.

5.3 AppsFuel uses web beacons and other such monitoring tools to follow your behaviour when visiting the Website, web app and using the services in order to get a better understanding of how you use the Website, web app and the services to as to improve the services provided to you. Such activities may include making recommendations for additional content and information which may be of interest and value to you based on your previous usage. However, you are no under obligation to read or utilise any of the facilities contained in them.

5.4 AppsFuel and our advertisers may use third-party companies to serve ads when you visit the marketplace. These third-party ad-serving companies may also place Cookies on your computer or mobile phone. Sometimes these Cookies may be used to provide targeted advertising to you. These advertising companies may also use web beacons to help manage and optimize our online advertising.

5.5 To the extent that AppsFuel allows advertisers or other third parties to use cookies or web beacons, AppsFuel will require that they agree to adopt a substantially similar privacy policy with respect to your information. Some third-party ad serving companies have agreed to allow users to opt-out of receiving targeted advertising. For more information see: http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp 

6\. IP Addresses

6.1 AppsFuel compiles logs of IP addresses of visitors to the Websites and the web app for administrative and analytical purposes. AppsFuel does not routinely collect any personally identifiable information through its compilation of IP address or the location of computers or mobile on the Internet. However, in cases of suspected abuse or service problems, AppsFuel may use an IP address in conjunction with other personally identifiable information to enforce our Terms of Use and/or to protect or troubleshoot the Apps, its users or others who may be affected. Except as provided in Section 6, below, AppsFuel will not share personally identifiable information associated with IP addresses or with third parties without your permission.

6.2 AppsFuel may share data about aggregate IP addresses, but such data does not include personally identifiable information except as set out below in Sharing Information. 

7\. Sharing of Information

7.1 AppsFuel may share personally identifiable information with third parties in the following cases:

a) to enable the normal course of functionality of the marketplace (. In some cases, AppsFuel may work with third parties that do analysis and development on our behalf. We may share your personally identifiable information with such a third-party on the condition that the third-party maintains the information as confidential and uses the information only to perform the services specified by AppsFuel; and/or

b) to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, to prevent fraud or imminent harm, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; and/or

c) in the event that AppsFuel is acquired by or merged with another company, AppsFuel will transfer information about you to that other company. In this event, AppsFuel will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy, and permit you to delete your account.

7.2 AppsFuel reserves the right to send you certain communications relating to the Websites and the web app and the services offered thereby, such as service announcements and administrative messages, but we plan on doing so sparingly, if ever. In any case, we reserve the right to contact you regarding violation of this privacy policy, the Terms of Use, and any other violation of law or applicable regulations and policies.

8\. Changes

8.1 AppsFuel may amend this privacy policy from time to time. If AppsFuel does so, the revised privacy policy will be posted on the Appsfuel page, and you will have the opportunity to modify your information on file with AppsFuel as explained below.

9\. Links to Other Sites and Apps

9.1 Appsfuel contains links to media and third parties apps. In addition, such third-party apps may also contain external links. Because of the dynamic media capabilities of the websites and web apps, it may not be clear to you which links are embedded in the websites and the web app and which are embedded in third parties media and/or content. Although AppsFuel requires our business partners and advertisers to adopt privacy policies similar to this privacy policy with respect to any information collected on the websites and the web app, AppsFuel cannot and does not guarantee the privacy policies and practices of any third-party. AppsFuel does not control, operate or endorse any information, products or services of any third party that may be reached through links from Appsfuel. The use of any personal information provided to such a third-party will be governed by that party's privacy policy. 

10\. Security

10.1 AppsFuel's site has reasonable security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while AppsFuel strives to protect your personal information, AppsFuel cannot ensure the security of any information that you transmit to AppsFuel or any information that you receive from AppsFuel's Service, and you transmit and receive such information at your own risk. Your AppsFuel registered user account information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. Please make sure to protect your account information and log off when you are done using AppsFuel, especially if other users have access to the same computer. 

11\. Acceptance

11.1 This privacy policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms and conditions of AppsFuel's Terms of Use, available on the website/ web app. Use of Appsfuel is subject to your compliance with the Terms of Use, which constitutes a legal agreement between you and AppsFuel. Each time you use Appsfuel signifies that you have read, understood and agree to be bound by the Terms of Use, which incorporates the privacy policy, and the applicable posted guidelines. USE OF APPSFUEL SIGNIFIES THE ACCEPTANCE OF THE TERMS OF USE AND THE PRIVACY POLICY. If you do not agree with the terms of either of these documents, please do not provide AppsFuel with any information and do not use Appsfuel. Your continued use of Appsfueland the services offered thereby in light of changes to this privacy policy, the Terms of Use, or to the relevant principles thereof will signify your acceptance of the changes. 

12\. Comments and Questions

12.1 If you have any comments or questions you may address them to our customer service department at [help@appsfuel.com](mailto:help@appsfuel.com)
